jobs = {
  "janitor": {
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "I DEMAND TO SPEAK TO YOUR MANAGER FOR SUCH A BAD CLEANING JOB",
        "response": ["i quit", "fine karen", "why me", "boss theres a karen", "why is this my life", "no", "nah", "stop", "okay", "ok"]
      },
      {
        "question": "clean this 30,000 square feet abandoned mall in the next half hour or you're fired.",
        "response": ["easy", "no", "why", "omg", "how", "ok", "cool", 'sure', "yes", "nah"]
      },
      {
        "question": "which of building you want to care take of",
        "response": ['office', 'apartment', 'home', 'area51', 'ur mom', "house", "building", "you", "your mom", "u"]
      },
      {
        "question": "your mop is broken. what do u do?",
        "response": ['give me new mop', "quit", 'i quit','die', 'idk', "idc", "go away", "get another one", "get new mop", "gimme one", "give me another one"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be promoted?",
        "response": ['nope', 'hate promotions', 'nah', 'no', 'no thanks']
      },
      {
        "question": "your shift is the basement",
        "response": ["yessir", "yes sir", "ok", "i love the basement", "best manager ever!", "yay", "nice", "bruh"]
      },
      {
        "question": "your pay will be 1 dollar a week.",
        "response": ["best pay", "ok", "great", "too high"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 50,
    "salary": 100,
    "fail": 10
  },
  "developer": {
    "tasks": [
      {
        "question": "bruh you suck",
        "response": ["yes", "i am", "agree"]
      },
      {
        "question": "ERROR: You're not an developer",
        "response": ["ok", 'nice', "cool"]
      },
      {
        "question": "what does this error mean?",
        "response": ["search google", "idk", "idc", "ask someone else"]
      },
      {
        "question": "how much google searching have you used",
        "response": ["yes", "no", "uh", "uhh", "uhhh", "none", "stackoverflow", "stackoverflow yes"]
      },
      {
        "question": "do you need help?",
        "response": ["yes", "im fine", "yes please", "help me", "everyone like everyone", "ofc"]
      },
      {
        "question": "help the other dev",
        "response": ["tell him to help me", "ok", "no i hate him", "fine", "no", "nah"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 1000,
    "salary": 500,
    "fail": 100
  },
  "pilot":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "Sir, we're missing 20 people.",
        "response": ["don't worry about the losers", "idk", "fine, we'll wait", "they better get here soon", "i killed them"]
      },
      {
        "question": "flight attendant: we have a code 432-45-34 A",
        "response": ["wtf", "wdym", "i quit", "what does that mean?", 'what']
      }
    ],
    "req": 5000,
    "salary": 1000,
    "fail": 250
  },
  "cook":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "OMG A RAT IN THE SOUP! WHAT YOU DO!",
        "response": ["eat", "ignore it", "ignore", "kill", "run", "soup", "leave it there", "leave it"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 500,
    "salary": 250,
    "fail": 50
  },
  "police":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "a criminal shot you in the heart, what do you do to him?",
        "response": ["shoot him back", "shoot him", "kill him", "kill", "shoot", "shot"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 2000,
    "salary": 400,
    "fail": 144
  },
  "amogus":{
    "tasks":[
      {"question": "AMOGUS!!!!",
      "response": ["amogus", "nice", "sus sus", "sus"]},
      {"question": "a stranger said AMOGUS. What would you say to him?",
      "response": ["amogus", "shut", "shut up", "imposter", "sus", "sus sus"]
      },
    ],
    "req": 10000,
    "salary": 1250,
    "fail": 1000
  },
  "solider":{
    "tasks":[
      {"question": "You were shot in the heart, brain and you're still alive! but what's your last words?",
      "response": ["bye", "bai", ".", "ok", "ok boomer"]},
    ],
    "req": 100,
    "salary": 150,
    "fail": 20
  },
  "doctor":{
    "tasks":[
      {"question": "Your parent: BECOME A BETTER DOCTOR! YOU LITERALLY CANNOT DO ANYTHING",
      "response": ["ok", "ok boomer", "im trying to", "i am trying to", "i'm trying to", "no", "nah", "idk"]},
    ],
    "req": 2500,
    "salary": 1000,
    "fail": 10
  },
}